Resume

Personal Information

Name: Fábio Garbato Age: 23 years old City: Curitiba - PR

Email: fabiogarbato3006@gmail.com

Phone: (41) 98737-2059

Education

High School: Colégio Objetivo Penha - High School

Graduation: Universidade Positivo - Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, from 2020 to 2023

Professional Summary

Developer with experience in HTML5, C#, .NET, MS-SQL Server, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6+), Delphi, Python, React.js, VueJS, Bootstrap, Node.js, PostgreSQL, MySQL and JSON REST APIs. Experience in Scrum, unit testing, Git (Gitea) and GitHub for code control and project versioning, as well as e-commerce development (B2B, B2C) with Magento.

Professional Experience

CCM do Brasil

FullStack Software Developer - June/2024 - Currently

- Development of web applications using React, Bootstrap, Node.js, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS
- Integration with Firebase for authentication and real-time database, as well as development of REST APIs
- Implementation of concurrent programming for process optimization and performance improvement of applications

MPS Informática

FullStack Developer - Jan/2024 - Currently

- Development of web applications with HTML5, CSS3, Node.js, React, Bootstrap, and Vue.js
- Maintenance of existing legacy systems with Delphi 7/XE
- Collaboration with multidisciplinary teams, using the SCRUM methodology
- Development of Python scripts for data extraction
- Development of REST APIs using C# and .NET

Junior Developer - Aug/2022 - Dec/2023

- Maintenance of existing legacy systems with Delphi 7/XE
- Development and maintenance of REST APIs using C# and .NET
- Collaboration with multidisciplinary teams, using the SCRUM methodology
- Creation of Procedures, Triggers, and Views in MS-SQL Server database
- Development of complex queries to support clients in MS-SQL Server database
- Unit Testing

Intern - Developer - Oct/2021 - Jul/2022

- Maintenance of existing legacy systems with Delphi 7/XE
- Development and maintenance of REST APIs using C# and .NET

Skills

Programming Languages: Python, Javascript (ES6+), Delphi 7/XE/10, C#, HTML5, CSS3 Frameworks: React, Node.js, VueJS, Express, Bootstrap, Flask, .NET 5.0/8.0, Sequelize

Databases: PostgreSQL, MySQL, SQL, MongoDB, Firebase

Tools: GitHub, Gitea, Tortoise SVN

Organization: Unit Testing, SCRUM Methodology

AWS: S3Client, Bucket and Object Management, Permission Configuration, Versioning Implementation, Integration with Lambda and CloudFront